Inventory of the Papers of Duke and Duke 1854-1956
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Case Files
  - 1890's
    - Yancey v. Burton 1896-1910 (Box 60)
  - 1900's
    - John H. Baber's Administrator 1908 (Box 61)
    - Burnley v. Burnley 1907 (Box 61)
    - Chaloner v. Sherman 1900-1911, 3 folders (Box 61)
    - C. B. Dickinson Estate 1880-1916 (Box 61)
    - Duke v. Minor 1900-1904 (Box 61)
    - William Durrett Estate 1908 (Box 61)
    - E. B. Gianninny 1900, 1903 (Box 61)
    - John Gibson 1903 (Box 61)
    - Gilmer v. Burkhead 1905 (Box 61)
    - J. Triplett Haxall 1902 (Box 61)
    - Huntington-Wayland Estates 1906-1924, 7 folders (Box 61-62)
    - Page v. Bird 1909, 1924-25, 1940, 3 folders (Box 62)
    - Rittenhaus tax matter 1908 (Box 62)
    - Robertson v. Harmon 1908-1927 (Box 62)
    - Fred G. Rust Estate 1900-1924, 7 folders (Box 62)
    - Sandridge Estate 1909-1924, 1936, 3 folders (Box 62)
    - Polly Smith's Administrator 1906 (Box 63)
    - W. E. Swann 1900-1912 (Box 63)
    - Via v.Coleman c. 1900 (Box 63)
    - John L. Walters Estate 1901-1927, 4 folders (Box 63)
    - Ware v. Pretlow c. 1910 (Box 63)
    - Waters v. Trefouret 1900 (Box 63)
    - W. F. Williams and Gianinny Trust Fund 1906 (Box 63)
  - 1910's
    - Albemarle Soapstone Co. v. Skipwith 1913 (Box 63)
    - American Surety Co. 1912 (Box 63)
    - Bainbridge v. County of Albemarle 1914-1915 (Box 63)
    - A. W. Barlow 1918-1925 (Box 63)
    - Barlow v. Barlow 1918 (Box 63)
    - W. H. Barlow's Estate 1914-1916 (Box 63)
    - Brigg's Electric Co. 1919-1920 (Box 63)
    - D. Walker Brown 1919-1943 (Box 63)
    - Brown v. Rinehart and Dennis Co. 1917 (Box 63)
    - Bucyrus Co. v. Rinehart and Dennis Co. 1914 (Box 63)
    - Burnap v. Rives 1911-1914 (Box 63)
    - J. W. Byer 1919-1925 (Box 63)
    - Carter v. Payne 1914 (Box 63)
    - Cheatham Hill Road 1913 (Box 63)
    - City of Charlottesville v. County of Albemarle 1916 (Box 63)
    - Cochran v. Bargamin 1912 (Box 63)
    - Lettie Ann Coles' Estate 1910-1913, 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia cases 1915 (Box 64)
    - Crowder v. Byer 1913-1915 (Box 64)
    - Davis v. Davis 1919-1941 (Box 63)
    - Duke v. City of Charlottesville 1911, 1915, 2 folders (Box 64)
    - Equitable Surety Co. 1912 (Box 64)
    - Garth v. C& O Railroad 1912 (Box 64)
    - Richard J. Gillium 1917-1918 (Box 64)
    - Goodwin v. Goodwin 1917-1920's (Box 64)
    - Curtis A. Haden 1915 (Box 64)
    - S. N. Harman Property 1912-1921 (Box 64)
    - Angeline v. Harris's Administrator 1912 (Box 64)
    - Lane Bros. Co. v. J. E. Lane and Co. 1916-1920 (Box 64)
    - Levy v. Red Land Power Co. 1913 (Box 64)
    - J. H. Lindsay 1916 (Box 64)
    - MacGovern and Co. 1915-1920 (Box 64)
    - E. H. Mason 1913 (Box 64)
    - Maupin v. Maupin 1914 (Box 64)
    - Miller v. Chaloner 1912-1917 (Box 64)
    - Tom Morris 1912-1918 (Box 65)
    - Tommy Nowlin 1915 (Box 64)
    - Payne v. Norris 1910 (Box 65)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Co. 1910-1913 (Box 65)
    - Platers' Co. v. City of Charlottesville 1918 (Box 65)
    - Miss J. Pretlow 1919 (Box 65)
    - Reid Estate c. 1910 (Box 65)
    - Rinehart and Dennis Co. v. J. C. Lipscomb and Co. 1914 (Box 65)
    - Rinehart and Dennis Co. v. Collier 1912-1916, 4 folders (Box 65)
    - Nannie D. Robinson 1918-1923 (Box 66)
    - Mary T. Scott Estate 1911-1913, 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Scruggs v. Scruggs 1918 (Box 66)
    - J. A. and E. W. Seins 1912 (Box 66)
    - Sherman v. Hewitt Construction Co. 1914 (Box 66)
    - Elizabeth H. Tompkins Estate 1910 (Box 66)
    - Updike 1919-1920 (Box 66)
    - Jessie S. Uppleby Estate 1918-1919 (Box 66)
    - John Uppleby Estate 1918-1919, 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Watson v. Western Union Telegraph Co. 1914 (Box 66)
    - White Sewing Machine Co. 1911 (Box 66)
    - Woolforth v. Fray 1912 (Box 66)
    - R. S. Worthington Estate c. 1913 (Box 66)
  - 1920's
    - Aetna Casualty & Surety Co. v. King Lumber Co. 1923, 3 folders (Box 67)
    - County of Albemarle v. Southern Railway Co. 1925 (Box 67)
    - Albemarle Electric Co. v. Preston 1923 (Box 67)
    - Albemarle Pole Co. 1929 (Box 67)
    - Alemite Lubricator Co. v. Skeen 1923-1925 (Box 67)
    - E. T. Alexander Estate 1926 (Box 67)
    - O. R. Allen 1923-1943, 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Allen and Williams, Inc. 1928-1933, 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Almirall and Co., Inc. v. King Lumber Co. 1924 (Box 67)
    - Aluminum-Fibre Limb Corp. v. Suddarth 1924 (Box 67)
    - Alvis v. Melton 1922 (Box 67)
    - R. S. Alvis 1923-1931, 2 folders (Box 67)
    - American Glass Works v. Crescent Drug Co. 1925 (Box 67)
    - American Glass Works v. Fitch's Drug Store 1926 (Box 67)
    - American Surety Co. v. Baker 1923 (Box 67)
    - Amprezes v. Pappas 1924-25 (Box 67)
    - Armour and Co. v. Burgess 1923-1924 (Box 67)
    - Miscellaneous case files--A 1920's (Box 67)
    - Baber v. Powell 1922-1923 (Box 67)
    - Bailey v. Jefferson Mills 1925-1927 (Box 67)
    - Sarah J. Baker 1921 (Box 67)
    - Barnett v. Cleland 1925 (Box 67)
    - Valdosia Barrett 1924 (Box 67)
    - Barringer v. Wood 1923-1924 (Box 68)
    - Barr v. Department of Agriculture 1922 (Box 68)
    - Basic City Bank v. Kirby 1923-1924 (Box 68)
    - Bass v. Kendig 1920 (Box 68)
    - Mrs. L. E. Bateman 1922-1923 (Box 68)
    - Baum's Castorine Co. v. Wood's Garage 1925 (Box 68)
    - Belew v. Belew 1924 (Box 68)
    - C. W. Belew 1926-1927 (Box 68)
    - Belew v. Allen 1925 (Box 68)
    - Belk v. Wayne Oil Tank and Pump Co. 1920 (Box 68)
    - Bickers v. Bickers 1924 (Box 68)
    - Bickers' settlements 1928-1932 (Box 68)
    - L. M. Blackford 1923, 1925 (Box 68)
    - Blair v. Blair 1922-1941 (Box 68)
    - Blair v. Whitworth 1925 (Box 68)
    - County of Albemarle v. Maupin 1920's (Box 68)
    - Mrs. Carroll Boocock 1924 (Box 68)
    - Samuel Bowles 1925 (Box 68)
    - Boyle-Robertson Construction Co. 1926-1927 (Box 68)
    - Bradbury v. Bradbury 1926 (Box 68)
    - Bragg v. Bragg 1924 (Box 68)
    - F. B. Bragg 1919-1926, 2 folders (Box 68)
    - F. R. Bragg and B. A. Bragg 1926-1929 (Box 68)
    - Bragg v. Wheeler 1929 (Box 68)
    - E. S. Branshaw 1924 (Box 68)
    - Brenard Mfg. Co. v. Covington 1920 (Box 68)
    - Fannie A. Brisco 1923-1930, 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Brookwood Farm 1926-1930, 3 folders (Box 69)
    - Brower v. Naylor 1925 (Box 69)
    - Brown Milling Co. v. U.S. Grain Corp. 1920-1921 (Box 69)
    - Browing v. Browing 1926 (Box 69)
    - A. C. Bruce 1920's (Box 69)
    - J. D. Burton 1926-1934 (Box 69)
    - Byrd v. Blincoe 1923-1925 (Box 69)
    - Miscellaneous case files--B 1925-1930 (Box 69)
    - Cabell v. Western Union Telegraph Co. 1923 (Box 69)
    - Anna F. Carter Estate 1920's (Box 69)
    - Carter Corp. v. Brown 1922 (Box 69)
    - Carter Corp. v. Grasty 1922 (Box 69)
    - Carter Corp. v. Union Bank 1921-1922 (Box 69)
    - Carter v. Smither 1923-1924 (Box 69)
    - Carter v. Tanner 1929-1930, 2 folders (Box 69)
    - Carver v. Bailey 1922 (Box 69)
    - Carver v. Graves 1927 (Box 69)
    - Lucy A. Carver Estate 1923-1939 (Box 69)
    - William Z. Catterton Estate 1923 (Box 69)
    - H. Christian 1929 (Box 69)
    - Chumas v. Hatton 1924 (Box 69)
    - City Loan Co. 1926 (Box 69)
    - City Loan Corp. 1925-1927 (Box 70)
    - City of Charlottesville v. Drake 1920's (Box 70)
    - City of Charlottesville v. Hall 1922 (Box 70)
    - Clark v. Rocbond Co. 1926 (Box 70)
    - Haniel Clark and Son v. Albemarle Mills Co. 1923-1924, 3 folders (Box 70)
    - Clarke v. Huff 1925 (Box 70)
    - Clay v. McCall 1924-1927 (Box 70)
    - John T. Clements 1922-1929 (Box 70)
    - Cloud v. Guerrant 1922 (Box 70)
    - Paul S. Coiner 1928 (Box 70)
    - Coleman v. Bridge Commissioners 1921 (Box 70)
    - Coleman-Smith Lumber Co. v. King Lumber Co. 1921-1924, 5 folders (Box 70)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. J.G. Ballard 1926 (Box 71)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Carroll 1924-1925 (Box 71)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Mahoney 1928-1929 (Box 71)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Zimmerman 1920's (Box 71)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Morris 1923 (Box 71)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Pugh 1924-1925 (Box 71)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Shiflett 1923 (Box 71)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Tanksley 1923 (Box 71)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Taylor 1922 (Box 71)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Via 1922-1923 (Box 71)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Wood 1922 (Box 71)
    - Miscellaneous commonwealth cases 1924-1925 (Box 71)
    - Commonwealth and Albemarle County Cases 1922 (Box 71)
    - Commonwealth: Forms, etc: 1923 (Box 71)
    - Congoleum Co. v. Nightengale 1923-1925 (Box 71)
    - Connelly and Co. v. Pflugradt 1925 (Box 71)
    - Cooper v. Leafe 1926 (Box 71)
    - Cory, Camp, Thomas 1924-1925 (Box 71)
    - Costen v. Fowler 1920's (Box 71)
    - Costan v. Smith 1924-1926 (Box 71)
    - Cowne v. Charlottesville Ice Co. 1924-1925 (Box 71)
    - G. S. Creasy 1924-1925 (Box 71)
    - Crenshaw v. Crenshaw 1928-1929, 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Crickenberger v. Crickenberger 1923 (Box 71)
    - Elizabeth Forbes Dallam 1929 (Box 71)
    - Davis v. Davis 1923-1924 (Box 71)
    - Davis Phonograph Co. v. Clements 1926 (Box 72)
    - DeJarnette v. Anderson 1926 (Box 72)
    - J. B. Dickinson sale 1923-1924 (Box 72)
    - T. W. Todd 1922-1925 (Box 72)
    - T. M. Dodson 1923-1936 (Box 72)
    - Dudley v. Dudley 1924 (Box 72)
    - Duff v. Carver 1926 (Box 72)
    - Pearl M. Duff 1923-1934, 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Duke v. Hertd 1927-1948 (Box 72)
    - Duke v. Walker 1922 (Box 72)
    - General--D 1922 (Box 72)
    - Mrs. M.J. Falconer 1925-1931 (Box 72)
    - Fallsburg Bridge Case 1922 (Box 72)
    - Fallsburg Power Corp. 1920-1922, 3 folders (Box 72)
    - Farish v. Farish 1922 (Box 72)
    - E. W. Feuchtenberger 1928 (Box 72)
    - Rosa N. Flewellen 1928 (Box 72)
    - Fox Brothers v. Barber 1929-1930 (Box 72)
    - City of Fredericksburg v. Yancey Ice Co. 1922 (Box 72)
    - Miscellaneous case files--E, F 1921-1926 (Box 72)
    - Garfield Bank 1926 (Box 73)
    - A. L. Garrison 1924-1926 (Box 73)
    - C. T. Garth and Fannie Michie 1921-1927 (Box 73)
    - Mrs. A. B. Garver 1925-1928 (Box 73)
    - T. Ivar Gedda 1927 (Box 73)
    - General Motors v. Thomas 1924-1925 (Box 73)
    - Gentry v. Ashley 1924 (Box 73)
    - Georges v. Nicholson 1925-1926 (Box 73)
    - Giles v. Thaw; Miscellaneous--G 1926-1934 (Box 73)
    - Gilliam v. Gilliam 1921 (Box 73)
    - James B. Gilmer 1923 (Box 73)
    - Goodyear v. Robertson 1924 (Box 73)
    - Guggenheimer v. Caufield 1921-1924, 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Gulley v. Fox Brothers 1927-1930 (Box 73)
    - Lizzie and Maude Gunther 1923-1950, 3 folders (Box 73)
    - Hagenbeck-Wallace Shows Co. v. Watkins 1926 (Box 73)
    - Hall v. Twyman 1922 (Box 73)
    - J. H. Tamer 1924 (Box 74)
    - F. M. Hamilton 1922, 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Mrs. C. N. Hancock 1924-1925 (Box 74)
    - Edith R. Harker Estate 1926 (Box 74)
    - Harley v. Sprouse 1929-1933 (Box 74)
    - Harlow v. Southern Railway; L. Fleming v. Southern Railway 1920 (Box 74)
    - Harlow v. Harlow 1921-1923 (Box 74)
    - Annie W. Harris 1920's (Box 74)
    - Harris v. Templeton 1922-1925 (Box 74)
    - Harris v. Harris; Drumheller bonds 1906 (Box 74)
    - Mary Jean Harris Estate 1923-1924, 3 folders (Box 74)
    - Mary, Annie, and Zella Harris 1922 (Box 74)
    - Harris Children and W. A. Harris Estate 1921-1926, 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Old Harris statements 1910's-1920's (Box 74)
    - Norvin T. Harris 1923 (Box 74)
    - Cornelia Harrison Estate 1922-1923 (Box 74-75)
    - Harrison v. Belew 1926 (Box 75)
    - William Argyle Harris Estate 1926-1940 (Box 75)
    - A. D. Hart Estate 1927 (Box 75)
    - Haynes v. Lineberger Mfg. Co. 1922 (Box 75)
    - John G. Henderson Estate 1928 (Box 75)
    - C. P. Herring 1922-1924 (Box 75)
    - Mary R. Hibbert 1923 (Box 75)
    - Highland Live Stock and Orchard Co. v. Via 1924-1925 (Box 75)
    - Hitt v. Templeton 1922 (Box 75)
    - Holbert v. Bowen 1922-1923 (Box 75)
    - Houchens v. Southern Railway 1922 (Box 75)
    - Lizzie Hughes Estate 1922-1923 (Box 75)
    - W. C. Hughes 1922-1938 (Box 75)
    - Humphreys v. Gibson 1926 (Box 75)
    - Humphreys v. Gibson 1926 (Box 75)
    - Hurt v. Lipscombe 1923-1925 (Box 76)
    - Hyde v. Bebout 1923-1925 (Box 76)
    - Dr. W. J. Jones 1924-1926 (Box 76)
    - W. J. Jones Estate 1926-1927, 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Kahn v. Hillhouse 1926 (Box 76)
    - Kanney v. Fox Brothers 1929-1931 (Box 76)
    - Joseph G. Kent 1926-1927 (Box 76)
    - King Lumber Co. v. Faulconer 1920's (Box 76)
    - King Lumber Co. v. Miller Safe Co. 1921 (Box 76)
    - W. E. Knight 1923 (Box 76)
    - Jackson Lafferty 1924-1927 (Box 76)
    - Lamb v. Lamb 1929 (Box 76)
    - Lang v. Hotchkiss 1926 (Box 76)
    - Lasley v. McCue 1928 (Box 76)
    - Belle Layne 1924 (Box 76)
    - F. C. Leake 1927 (Box 76)
    - P. H. Leake Estate 1923-1924 (Box 76)
    - Rebecca R. Lee 1922-1923 (Box 76)
    - Molly Lewis Estate c. 1920, copy of 1820 (Box 76)
    - Liberty Feed Co. v. Garth 1927-1929 (Box 76)
    - Lipps v. Walker 1926-1930 (Box 76)
    - Liquid Carbonic Co. v. Charlottesville Candy Kitchen 1925 (Box 76)
    - Liquid Carbonic Co. v. Virginia Pepsi Cola Bottling Co. 1924-1925 (Box 76)
    - Loose papers from case files 1920's-1930's (Box 77)
    - William Malone Estate 1926-1927 (Box 77)
    - Marable v. Buckner 1927-1935 (Box 77)
    - Marshal v. Collier 1926 (Box 77)
    - J. W. Marshall 1923-1924 (Box 77)
    - Marshall Mfg. Co. v. Charlottesville Lumber Co. 1920-1921 (Box 77)
    - Maryland-Virginia Milk Products Co. v. Rothwell 1925-1929 (Box 77)
    - McIntosh v. McIntosh 1926-1928 (Box 77)
    - C. B. McKennie 1921-1929 (Box 77)
    - G. M. McNutt Estate 1922-1926 (Box 77)
    - McNutt v. Dexter 1924-1925 (Box 77)
    - Michawaka Rubber and Woolen Mfg. Co. v. Kidd 1928-1929 (Box 77)
    - Fannie M. Michie Estate 1926 (Box 77)
    - Helen A. Michie 1924-1926 (Box 77)
    - Milk Products Co. v. City of Charlottesville 1925-1929 (Box 77)
    - Miller v. Fisher Bus Co. 1926 (Box 77)
    - Miller v. Leedy 1926 (Box 77)
    - Miller v. Phillips 1927-1932, 3 folders (Box 77)
    - Miller v. Rothwell 1923-1929, 3 folders (Box 77)
    - Moller v. West 1923-1924 (Box 78)
    - W. E. Money Estate 1925-1927 (Box 78)
    - Monticello Dairy v. Bass 1926-1927 (Box 78)
    - Monticello Dairy v. Crescent Drug Co. 1926 (Box 78)
    - Monticello Dairy v. Ellerslie Co-op Dairy 1927 (Box 78)
    - Monticello Dairy v. Hughes 1928 (Box 78)
    - Monticello v. Reedy 1925 (Box 78)
    - Monticello Dairy v. Zero Products Co. 1927 (Box 78)
    - Morgan v. Weaver 1920-1933, 4 folders (Box 78)
    - Morgan v. Estes 1920-1921 (Box 78)
    - Nellie Maud Morrice Estate 1925-1927 (Box 78)
    - Pauline Moubray 1926 (Box 78)
    - Lucy E. Munday 1922-1923 (Box 78)
    - W. B. Murphy 1923 (Box 78)
    - Musick v. Glenham 1927 (Box 78)
    - National Bank of Charlottesville v. Ryan 1921 (Box 78)
    - Newman v. Newman 1922-1923 (Box 78)
    - Newport Sand Bank Co. v. Walker 1925 (Box 78)
    - Norvell v. Norvell 1923-1924, 2 folders (Box 78)
    - Nowlin v. Thomas (sa Thomas v. Nowlin) c. 1922 (Box 78)
    - Nuchapep, Inc. 1927-1930, 2 folders (Box 78)
    - Ferrell v. Wheeler 1926 (Box 79)
    - Otter v. Lindsay 1923 (Box 79)
    - Mr. and Mrs. J. Shepherd Parrish 1920-1930 (Box 79)
    - Payton v. Ramby 1923 (Box 79)
    - Pence and Sterling v. Craig 1923 (Box 79)
    - Pence and Sterling v. Kelley 1923-1924 (Box 79)
    - Penny Profit Store v. Via 1920-1922 (Box 79)
    - H. P. Porter 1921-1944, 4 folders (Box 79)
    - Porter and Hanckel 1929 (Box 79)
    - Powell v. Brandenburg 1928-1956, 3 folders (Box 79)
    - Powell v. Powell 1923-1925 (Box 80)
    - Powell v. Wood 1926 (Box 80)
    - Powers and Anderson Dental Co. v. Miller 1923 (Box 80)
    - Prudential Insurance Co. v. Pitts 1928 (Box 80)
    - Raines v. H. M. Gleason Co. 1929 (Box 80)
    - Reynolds v. Reynolds 1924 (Box 80)
    - Richmond Dairy Co. v. Charlottesville Ice Co. 1925-1926 (Box 80)
    - Roberts v. Roberts 1924 (Box 80)
    - Alexander Robertson Estate 1922-1924 (Box 80)
    - Roth Downs Mfg. Co. v. Albemarle Electric Co. 1925-1926 (Box 80)
    - Roth Downs Mfg. Co. v. Hamm 1926-1928 (Box 80)
    - Mrs. Luther R. Sandridge 1923 (Box 80)
    - Mrs. S. W. Saunders 1926 (Box 80)
    - J. P. Sensibaugh 1924-1926 (Box 80)
    - Sensibaugh and Gibbs 1927-1930 (Box 80)
    - J. H. Shepherd and C. N. Wisner 1929 (Box 80)
    - Harry Shiflett Estate 1926 (Box 80)
    - J. E. Simpson 1921-1937, 2 folders (Box 80)
    - Slaughter v. Clark 1925 (Box 80)
    - Maude D. Smith 1923-1926 (Box 80)
    - Smith Electric Co. 1928 (Box 80)
    - Southern Bond Mortgage Co. 1928-1931 (Box 80)
    - Specialty Trading Co. v. M. A. West Music Co. 1923 (Box 80)
    - Mary Speed 1922-1923 (Box 80)
    - Stallings v. Newman 1925 (Box 80)
    - Standard Brick Co. (P. S. Yancey) 1923-1924 (Box 80)
    - Standard Education Society v. Scott 1923-1925 (Box 80)
    - Standard Paint Co. v. H. B. Sparks 1921-1925 (Box 80)
    - Swartz v. Bender 1925 (Box 81)
    - Miscellaneous case files--L-S 1920's (Box 81)
    - Talbot v. Croft 1924 (Box 81)
    - Thomas v. Nowlin (sa Nowlin v. Thomas) 1922 (Box 81)
    - Ben H. Thompson 1927 (Box 81)
    - Thompson v. Herbert 1923 (Box 81)
    - Mabel Thompson 1922 (Box 81)
    - F. G. Thorp 1923-1946, 2 folders (Box 81)
    - Lucius Timberlake 1929-1932 (Box 81)
    - Timberlake v. Smith 1928-1930 (Box 81)
    - Towles Estate 1920-1928, 6 folders (Box 81)
    - Tripolos v. Costan 1924-1925 (Box 81)
    - United Provisions Corp. v. Watts 1925 (Box 81)
    - United Provisions Corp. v. White 1925 (Box 81)
    - U.S. v. Hoback 1923 (Box 82)
    - United Trust Co. v. Harris 1923-1925 (Box 82)
    - Via v. Waters 1925 (Box 82)
    - Via v. Via 1921-1924, 2 folders (Box 82)
    - Mary D. Via 1924-1925 (Box 82)
    - Annie Viars 1923-1943 (Box 82)
    - Viars v. Kirby c. 1927-1929 (Box 82)
    - Miscellaneous case files--V 1924-1928 (Box 82)
    - Wade v. City of Charlottesville 1927-1928 (Box 82)
    - Mrs. George Walker 1922-1923 (Box 82)
    - Weber v. Rogers 1925 (Box 82)
    - B. E. Wheeler 1923-1927, 4 folders (Box 82-83)
    - V. M. Wheeler and C. H. Kirtley 1928-1929 (Box 83)
    - White v. Haden 1924 (Box 83)
    - F. L. Williams 1928-1931 (Box 83)
    - Williams v. Payton 1929-1930 (Box 83)
    - Mrs. Marion C. Wiatt 1923-1925 (Box 83)
    - Wilson v. Cocke 1925 (Box 83)
    - Midred Wood 1925-1928 (Box 83)
    - Wood v. Hayden 1929 (Box 83)
    - Worthington Hardware Co. v. Bedden 1927 (Box 83)
    - Wyant v. Conrad 1923-1925 (Box 83)
    - Yancey v. Yancey 1920's, 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Miscellaneous case files--T-Z 1920's (Box 83)
  - 1930's
    - Abbott and Holt Funeral Home v. Reed 1936 (Box 84)
    - Adams v. Edwards 1935-1936, 18 folders (Box 84-85)
    - Reliable Clothes v. Alexander 1935 (Box 85)
    - R. S. Alvis 1930 (Box 85)
    - Ambroselli Amusement Co.--Old Dominion Theatre 1934 (Box 85)
    - American Surety Co.--Bettie B. Glenn 1931-1938 (Box 85)
    - Evelyn Norford Anderson 1938-1939 (Box 85)
    - Austin Organ Co. v. High Street Baptist Church 1928-1935, 14 folders (Box 86-87)
    - Avery v. P. Lorillard Co. Inc 1937-1938, 4 folders (Box 87)
    - C. C. Baker and M. W. Brisco 1930's (Box 88)
    - Baker v. Walker 1936 (Box 88)
    - Mrs. G. C. Baker, Mrs. W. W. Osborne 1934-1939 (Box 88)
    - P. G. Baker 1936 (Box 88)
    - Barnett v. Lasley 1939-1941 (Box 88)
    - Henry E. Batcheller 1931-1932 (Box 88)
    - Edmund Berkeley 1938-1944 (Box 88)
    - F. L. Berkeley 1938 (Box 88)
    - Bingler v. Gay 1936 (Box 88)
    - E. Blake -- Russell Collision 1934 (Box 88)
    - Boling v. Massachusetts 1934 (Box 88)
    - Boling v. Western Assurance Co. 1930 (Box 88)
    - Botlen v. Lohr 1931 (Box 88)
    - Brown v. Hodges 1934-1938 (Box 89)
    - Isabella Burnett 1931-1934 (Box 89)
    - M. Estelle Burthe 1930 (Box 89)
    - Buttery v. Robbins 1938-1948, 7 folders (Box 89)
    - Albert v. Caffey 1938-1939 (Box 89)
    - Broadnax Cameron 1930-1936, 10 folders (Box 90-91)
    - Carickhoff v. M. E. Gillioz, Inc. 1937 (Box 91)
    - Carpenter v. Carpenter 1936 (Box 91)
    - Carpenter v. Colvin 1936-1937 (Box 91)
    - Anne H. Carter Estate 1936 (Box 91)
    - Thomas Carter Estate 1937 (Box 91)
    - Mann H. Cason 1936-1938 (Box 91)
    - Central Lumber Co. v. Mitchell 1931-1932 (Box 91)
    - Central United Coal Co. v. City Coal Co. 1932-1933 (Box 91)
    - Chester v. Shiflett 1937 (Box 91)
    - George A. Chisholm Estate 1937-1940 (Box 91)
    - Alice Coles 1939 (Box 91)
    - Coles v. Chisholm 1932 (Box 91)
    - Collins v. Culbertson 1932 (Box 91)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Bibb 1938 (Box 91)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Blakey 1937 (Box 91)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Dinwiddie 1936 (Box 91)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Griffin 1937-1940 (Box 91)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. Trice 1936-1937 (Box 92)
    - Cox v. Wood 1930 (Box 92)
    - Criser v. Bee 1931-1937, 6 folders (Box 92)
    - Davis v. Hoffa 1937 (Box 92)
    - Julia Davis 1932-1933 (Box 92)
    - Dean v. M. E. Gillioz, Inc 1937 (Box 92)
    - Dickinson v. Dickinson 1937 (Box 92)
    - Sybil J. Disney 1934-1937 (Box 92)
    - Dixie Flying Service, Inc. 1930 (Box 92)
    - Doyle v. Cold Springs Mining Co. 1935-1936 (Box 93)
    - Driver v. Cheetham 1934-1935 (Box 93)
    - Drumheller v. Richfield Oil Corp. 1939, 6 folders (Box 93)
    - L. W. Dudley c. 1930's (Box 93)
    - Dunn v. Smith 1937 (Box 93)
    - Engart v. Postal Telegraph 1931 (Box 93)
    - Estes v. U.S. 1932-1939 (Box 93)
    - Ezekial and Weilman Co. v. Fekas 1933-1934 (Box 93)
    - Fallert v. Pearlman 1936 (Box 94)
    - Farrish v. Farrish 1937 (Box 94)
    - Ferry-Morse Seed Co. v. Nay 1932-1934 (Box 94)
    - Ferry-Morse Seed Co. v. Whitten 1936-1937 (Box 94)
    - Bussinger v. Marks 1931-1932 (Box 94)
    - Fleming v. Garth 1937 (Box 94)
    - Fountain v. Fountain 1939 (Box 94)
    - Jonathan Garrison heirs and General file--G 1934-1935 (Box 94)
    - Miletus Garrison and Miscellaneous case files--G 1933-1934 (Box 94)
    - Garrison v. Garrison 1937 (Box 94)
    - Garrod v. Bowles 1938 (Box 94)
    - Dorothy Roosevelt Geer 1936 (Box 94)
    - Gibson v. Wheat 1937 (Box 94)
    - Gipson v. Gipson 1934 (Box 94)
    - Glass v. Charles Schwartz and Son 1932-1935 (Box 94)
    - Glidden Co. v. Burgess 1931 (Box 94)
    - Glidden Co. v. Hartman 1932-1933 (Box 94)
    - Greene, Whitney and Miller re P. G. Baker 1933 (Box 94)
    - H. Y. Gunby and Walter J. Moore re University Diner 1934-1935 (Box 94)
    - Hamm v. Marcus 1931-1932, 9 folders (Box 94-95)
    - Haney v. Haney 1930-1938 (Box 95)
    - Elizabeth M. Hardesty 1939-1940 (Box 95)
    - Bessie Harmon 1931-1939 (Box 95)
    - Harmon v. Eisner 1939 (Box 95)
    - Harrington v. Carver 1931 (Box 95)
    - Harris v. Thomas 1930's (Box 95)
    - Hartman v. Wylie 1937-1938, 2 folders (Box 95)
    - Hayman v. Scott 1934 (Box 95)
    - Hayman v. Bibb 1937 (Box 95)
    - Henderlite v. Oliver 1938-1939 (Box 95)
    - Henderson v. Henderson 1931 (Box 95)
    - Hermitage Ice and Storage, Inc. v. Bargamin 1931-1932 (Box 96)
    - Mary R. Hershey--Pennsylvania Manufacturers' Association 1935-1937 (Box 96)
    - Hewlett v. Schadel Insurance 1932-1934 (Box 96)
    - Houchens v. Barksdale, Harris, Powell and Powell 1931-1932, 2 folders (Box 96)
    - William Hughes 1932 (Box 96)
    - W. H. Robbins 1934-1935 (Box 96)
    - International Typewriter Exchange v. White 1933-1934 (Box 96)
    - Jackson v. Charlottesville Motor Co., Inc.; Jackson v. Universal Credit Co. 1937 (Box 96)
    - Jones v. Southworth 1938 (Box 96)
    - Jordan v. Atlantic Lead and Zinc Co. 1930-1932, 2 folders (Box 96)
    - Jordan v. Catania 1930-1931 (Box 96)
    - Nick Kardos 1936 (Box 96)